Contact

bobbyduracel@mac.com

www.linkedin.com/in/robert-conner-18b13247 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ICU

Critical Care

Healthcare

Certifications

NRP

TPATC

WFR

BLS

Certified Flight Registered Nurse

Robert Conner

MS-RN, MBA, CFRN, CCRN

Greater Denver Area

Summary

Experienced Flight Nurse & Critical Care RN with a demonstrated history of success in the hospital & health care industry. Strong healthcare services professional skilled in LVAD, STEMI, Stroke, EVD, Sepsis, TNCC, TPATC, NIHSS, NRP, Cardiothoracic Surgery, Nursing Education, Neurosurgery, Trauma, Rapid Response, Pediatrics, Emergency Medicine and Critical Care Transport. Former combat medic, hospital corpsman, and phlebotomist. I have nearly 20 years of healthcare experience & recently completed my MSN/MBA with a focus on leadership within healthcare organizations.

Experience

Centura Health

5 years 8 months

Nursing Manager

October 2019 - Present (9 months)

Greater Denver Area

Charge Nurse - Emergency Department January 2016 - October 2019 (3 years 10 months)

Durango, Colorado

Flight Nurse

November 2014 - January 2017 (2 years 3 months)

Durango, Colorado

Flight Nurse

Team EMS

Director Of Operations

January 2016 - Present (4 years 6 months)

Colorado

Dignity Health

ICU RN Traveler

May 2014 - November 2014 (7 months)

Page 1 of 3

Dominican Hospital

Banner Health
CVICU RN Traveler
December 2013 - April 2014 (5 months)
Banner Good Samaritan Hospital

Harborview Medical Center ICU Float Pool RN Traveler June 2013 - September 2013 (4 months) Seattle, WA

Barrow Neurological Institute ICU RN - Float Pool traveler November 2012 - May 2013 (7 months) Phoenix, AZ

St. Joseph's Hospital and Medical Center Float Pool ICU RN Traveler November 2012 - May 2013 (7 months) Phoenix, AZ

Sentara Healthcare RN - Advanced Heart Failure Unit Traveler July 2011 - December 2011 (6 months) Norfolk, Virginia Area

Tenet Healthcare
ICU BSN/RN
April 2008 - April 2011 (3 years 1 month)
Neurosurgical ICU

Wyman Teen Leadership Program
Camp RN
May 2008 - August 2009 (1 year 4 months)

U.S. Navy Reserve Hospital Corpsman March 2003 - March 2006 (3 years 1 month)

Kansas City Internal Medicine (KCIM)

Page 2 of 3

Phlebotomist 2003 - 2006 (3 years)

American Health Laboratory Phlebotomist 2001 - 2004 (3 years)

United States Army Reserve Combat Medical Specialist January 1997 - January 2000 (3 years 1 month)

Education

Grand Canyon University
MSN/MBA, Business and Healthcare Administration · (2016 - 2019)

Saint Louis University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2007 - 2008)